Tobi Samuel OJO

+2348132782405 | Moniya Area, Ibadan | tobisamuel197@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/tobisamuel

SUMMARY

Reliable, energetic, competent, resourceful, and detail conscious graduate of Management and Accounting who has keen interest in finance, and technology with over 3 years' experience in developing website applications. I am enthusiastic about learning and discovering new things, taking up new and challenging task(s) where the skills acquired will be applied, tested, and strengthened. Expertise in Website Programming, Book Keeping, Finance, Financial Reporting and Management.

WORK EXPERIENCE

ICONSMS Developer – https://www.iconsms.com.ng. (A VTU Web Application SwiftGeek Links

November, 2020

August, 2020

Full Stack Web Developer – https://www.swiftgeek.com.ng. (A VTU Web Application)

- Received satisfactory rating from customers and the manager after completing the website
- Effectively managed the company's website.

Nigeria Christian Corpers' Fellowship

State Media and Publicity Secretary & Caretaker (NCCF)

May 2019 - January, 2020

- Publication of the organization articles, newsletters, sending and receiving of emails on behalf of the organization
- Designed for the fellowship
- Maintained accurate records of the funds collected in concise, clear, and understandable manner.
- Effectively communicates with the stakeholders of the organization to ensure compliances with resolutions particularly as it concerns finance.

All Souls' Anglican Grammar School, Ado-Ekiti, Ekiti State Economics Teacher (NYSC)

March 2019 – March 2020

- Prepared and delivered lessons to secondary students of different learning abilities.
- Accurately marked the students' assessments; maintained records of the students' progress, and give appropriate feedback.
- Effectively researched new topic areas and maintained up-to-date subject knowledge.

Private (Holiday) Tutor, Ibadan

2013

Home Lesson Teacher- Ibadan, Oyo State

(Quantitative and verbal reasoning, Math, Account, Commerce, Economics, Biology)

 Responsible for tutoring and mentoring of grade (primary) and high school students after I finished high school in 2013

EDUCATION

- Obafemi Awolowo University B.SC. Management and Accounting
- February 2018

- Second Class(Hons)
- Providence High School

SKILLS

- Mastery of Microsoft Office Suites (Word, Excel, PowerPoint), and SPSS
- Intermediate in the use of SAGE50 (Peachtree)
- Digital skills such as Graphics, Video Editing, and Programming skills such as PHP, JavaScript, Angular, and Ionic.
- Excellent communication skills, inter and intra personal relationship skills with a focus on teambuilding and customer relations.
- Time management, outstanding organizational, multitasking, and problem-solving abilities.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Service Delivery – *Community Development Service Group, NYSC.*

May 2nd, 2019

Motto: Service to Humanity

U- Report – News Organization

April, 2019

 Worked as a team to collect phone numbers from people and register them with U-Report in order for them to report any issue or complaints in their respective locality

AWARDS AND HONORS

NCCF - Nigeria Christian Corpers' Fellowship

Ekiti State Media & Publicity Secretary

February 23rd, 2020

Worked closely with my team to complete assigned tasks and activities.

Digital Deepak Institute - Certified Digital Marketer

2017

• Took an online Course on Digital Marketing

PROFESSIONAL MEMBERSHIPS

Nigeria Institute of Management

March 2020 - Present

HOBBIES

Reading | Playing Ludo | Programming | Teaching | Basketball

LANGUAGE COMPETENCIES

Yoruba: Native | English: Conversational | French: Basic (Writing, Reading, and Speaking).

REFEREE

Prof O. Adewoye,

• (Rt) Ex-Lecturer at University of Ibadan - 08051547800.

Mr. Ajide Oluwamayowa

- CEO Wisdom Hub Initiative
- Manager at SeedVest Ekiti State, Nigeria-(08153873721)